Guide to the Asian CineVision Records TAM.416
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Video Recordings
  - Video 1107: Rebop:, cuid2372 (Box 165)
  - Video 1108: Sewing Woman by Arthur Dong, cuid2373 (Box 165)
  - Video 1109: Then by Takuhiro Tanaka and Shigeyeshi Ohi, cuid2374 (Box 165)
  - Video 1110: Third World Cultural Perspective Tape 1 by Nancy Tong/ Cecile Guidote, cuid2375 (Box 165)
  - Video 1111: The Young Concubine Part I by Wong King-Keung, 1981; cuid2376 (Box 165)
  - Video 1112: The Young Concubine Part II by Wong King-Keung, 1981; cuid2377 (Box 165)
  - Video 1113: Dangerous Encounter for the First Kind Part I by RTV, cuid2378 (Box 166)
  - Video 1114: Crack Shadow Boxers Part I, cuid2379 (Box 166)
  - Video 1115: Crack Shadow Boxers Part II, cuid2380 (Box 166)
  - Video 1116: Dangerous Encounter for the First King Part II by RTV, cuid2381 (Box 166)
  - Video 1117: The Imp (Pt. I), cuid2382 (Box 166)
  - Video 1118: The Mysterious Foot-Work of Kung Fu Part I, cuid2383 (Box 166)
  - Video 1119: The Mysterious Foot-Work of Kung Fu Part II, cuid2384 (Box 166)
  - Video 1120: Rainbow by Fung Fay Fay, cuid2385 (Box 166)
  - Video 1121: Reincarnated Part I by RTV, 1984; cuid2386 (Box 166)
  - Video 1122: The New Wife by Renee Cho (31 min), cuid2387 (Box 167)
  - Video 1123: A Piece of Cake (about Wayne Thiebaud) by Louise Lo (28'45") You Can't Lick Stamps in China by Nan June Park (28'39"), cuid2388 (Box 167)
  - Video 1124: Sichuan Acrobatic Feats Part I, cuid2389 (Box 167)
  - Video 1125: Sichuan Acrobatic Feats Part II, cuid2390 (Box 167)
  - Video 1126: Something is Rotten in Little Tokyo by Tom Kochiyama (37 min), cuid2391 (Box 167)
  - Video 1127: Strangle for Life, cuid2392 (Box 167)
  - Video 1128: Third World Cultural Perspective by La Mama Production Tape 1 of 2, cuid2393 (Box 167)
  - Video 1129: Third World Cultural Perspective by La Mama Production Tape 2 of 2, cuid2394 (Box 167)
  - Video 1130: With Silk Wings by Asian American Women at Work (30 min), cuid2395 (Box 167)
  - Video 1131: Bean Sprouts: Try it, You'll like it by Loni Ding, cuid2396 (Box 168)
  - Video 1132: The Boy Who Played with the Lion/Dragon by Sam Hom (Video Dub of Film), cuid2397 (Box 168)
  - Video 1133: East Meets West Channel 2 "The People", cuid2398 (Box 168)
  - Video 1134: Freckled Rice Excerpts by Stephen C. Ning, cuid2399 (Box 168)
  - Video 1135: Gold Dagger Romance Part I by RTV, 1984; cuid2400 (Box 168)
  - Video 1136: Heritage: Sail to the Southern Sea by RTHK, cuid2401 (Box 168)
  - Video 1137: Rebop: Ching Family, cuid2402 (Box 168)
  - Video 1138: Return of the Gangster, cuid2403 (Box 168)
  - Video 1139: Yellow Ball Workshop Children's Films, cuid2404 (Box 168)
  - Video 1140: "Golden Gate" Trailer, cuid2405 (Box 169)
  - Video 1141: Lick, 1995; cuid2406 (Box 169)
  - Video 1142: Requiem, cuid2407 (Box 169)
  - Video 1143: Say You Say Me, cuid2408 (Box 169)
  - Video 1144: The Shaolin Invincible Part I, cuid2409 (Box 169)
  - Video 1145: The Shaolin Invincible Part II, cuid2410 (Box 169)
  - Video 1146: "Stretchmark" Directed by Veena Cabreros-Sud, 1996; cuid2411 (Box 169)
  - Video 1147: War's Over, cuid2412 (Box 169)
  - Video 1148: "The Wedding Banquet" Trailer, cuid2413 (Box 169)
  - Videos 1149-1163: PALM (Philippine Alternative Media) tapes, 1981-1984; cuid2414 (Box 170)
  - Videos 1164- 1174 (small " tapes): WNYC Changing Faces of Chinatown tapes, cuid2415 (Box 171)
  - Video 1175: Asian Images in the Media by Bernice Chu, 1984; cuid2416 (Box 172)
  - Video 1176: CCTV Sample tape, cuid2417 (Box 172)
  - Video 1177: CCTV Sample tape, cuid2418 (Box 172)
  - Video 1178: Children's Film Series 1987, 1989; cuid2419 (Box 172)
  - Video 1179: Chinatown: 1984 (sample tape), cuid2420 (Box 172)
  - Video 1180: How to Become a Fascinating Speaker by Fu-Ding Cheng, 1989; cuid2421 (Box 172)
  - Video 1181: Tracking On (Master) (AAIVF comm..), cuid2422 (Box 172)
  - Video 1182: Tracking on (Raw Footage), cuid2423 (Box 172)
  - Video 1183: Vincent Chin "Remembrance Day" 6/19/83, 1984; cuid2424 (Box 172)
  - Video 1184: The Departure by Emiko Omori, 1984; cuid2425 (Box 173)
  - Video 1185: John by Art Nomura, 1989; cuid2426 (Box 173)
  - Video 1186: NAATA Press Conference: Portest WNET/13 censorship of Silkscreen series by Nancy Tong, 1984; cuid2427 (Box 173)
  - Video 1187: Stan Egi, comedian from David Letterman show; 1/31/85, cuid2428 (Box 173)
  - Video 1188: Two Comedians: Phil Nee and Stan Egi at the Middle of the Road (1/6/86), cuid2429 (Box 173)
  - Video 1189: Two Comedians: Phil Nee and Stan Egi at the Middle of the Road (1/6/86), cuid2430 (Box 173)
  - Video 1190: Two Comedians: Phil Nee and Stan Egi at the Middle of the Road (1/6/86), cuid2431 (Box 173)
  - Video 1191: Wallow (Silent) by Eiko and Koma, 1989; cuid2432 (Box 173)
  - Video 1192: We Have to Link, 1982; cuid2433 (Box 173)
  - Video 1193: "Ablutions" by S. Ashraf Mfer, 1993; cuid2434 (Box 174)
  - Video 1194: All Orientals Look the Same by Valerie Soe, cuid2435 (Box 174)
  - Video 1195: The Departure by Emiko Omori, cuid2436 (Box 174)
  - Video 1196: Husk by Eiko and koma, cuid2437 (Box 174)
  - Video 1197: Keyboard Dance by Ye Sook Rhee, cuid2438 (Box 174)
  - Video 1198: The Only Language She Knows by Steven Okazaki, cuid2439 (Box 174)
  - Video 1199: Snipers in the Trees by Curtis Choy 1985, cuid2440 (Box 174)
  - Video 1200: Stereotypes of Asian in the Media by ACV (AAE), cuid2441 (Box 174)
  - Video 1201: The Year of the Ox: The 1975 Chinatown Livestock Show by Curtis Choy, cuid2442 (Box 174)
  - Video 1202: After Image of Vanished Ways Featuring Sandy Granich, by Daryl Sujakawg, cuid2443 (Box 175)
  - Video 1203: Aquino Memorial Mass, September 1983, Shot by L. Remoador, M. Gener, R. Hodel, D. Miyazake, Produced by PALM (Philippine Alternative Media) a division of ACV, cuid2444 (Box 175)
  - Video 1204: Building Blocks and Tsumiki by Saiki Hiromu, cuid2445 (Box 175)
  - Video 1205: Ch'unhyang: Part 1, Tape 1, cuid2446 (Box 175)
  - Video 1206: Chinatown: 1984 (excerpt from part 1 of a 4 part series), cuid2447 (Box 175)
  - Video 1207: Coverage on the Year of the Dragon, 8/16/85, on CBS, NBC, ABC, Entertainment Tonight, cuid2448 (Box 175, Box Shared Tamiment 111)
  - Video 1208: "Marco Polo" Clips from NBC Production Featuring Ying Ruocheng as Kublai Khan, cuid2449 (Box 175)
  - Video 1209: Q it Up by Spencer Naka sako 1985, cuid2450 (Box 175)
  - Video 1210: The Electronic Sounds of Russell Baba (excerpts), cuid2451 (Box 175)
  - Video 1211: 1984 AAIVF footage, cuid2452 (Box 176)
  - Video 1212: CCTV (Chinese), cuid2453 (Box 176)
  - Video 1213: Charlie Chin, cuid2454 (Box 176)
  - Video 1214: Charlie Chin, cuid2455 (Box 176)
  - Video 1215: Chase scene tape #1, cuid2456 (Box 176)
  - Video 1216: HK Fashion Show CCTV, cuid2457 (Box 176)
  - Video 1217: An hon Kong Voyage by Sam Hom, 1979; cuid2458 (Box 176)
  - Video 1218: Josephine Cheng, cuid2459 (Box 176)
  - Video 1219: With Liberty and Justice for All, cuid2460 (Box 176)
  - Videos 1220-1228 (small " tapes): ACV Video Training Workshop tapes, cuid2461 (Box 177)
  - Video 1229: 1987 Video Production Workshop, cuid2462 (Box 178)
  - Video 1230: 1987 Video Production Workshop, cuid2463 (Box 178)
  - Video 1231: 1987 Video Production Workshop, cuid2464 (Box 178)
  - Video 1232: 1988 Video Production Workshop, cuid2465 (Box 178)
  - Video 1233: 1989 Workshop, cuid2466 (Box 178)
  - Video 1234: 1989 Video Production Workshop, cuid2467 (Box 178)
  - Video 1235: Asian Cinevision Presents Chinese American Television (sample tape), cuid2468 (Box 178)
  - Video 1236: Black for editing use only, cuid2469 (Box 178)
  - Video 1237: Standby tape, cuid2470 (Box 178)
  - Video 1238: Asian Films: Asian Film Series, 1986; cuid2471 (Box 179)
  - Video 1239: "Asian Cinevision Presents" Trailer, 1988; cuid2472 (Box 179)
  - Video 1240: Asian Cinevision, 1990; cuid2473 (Box 179)
  - Video 1241: Woo Art, cuid2474 (Box 179)
  - Video 1242: opening trailer, cuid2475 (Box 179)
  - Video 1243: Asian Cinevision, cuid2476 (Box 179)
  - Video 1244: "Videoscape", cuid2477 (Box 179)
  - Video 1245: "Kim Chi's Vietnam", cuid2478 (Box 179)
  - Video 1246: What Do You Know About Korea? (1996), cuid2479 (Box 179)
  - Video 1247: 60 flowers, 70 capsules, 80 digits by Arturo Cubacub, cuid2480 (Box 180)
  - Video 1248: Alpha Echo, The Journey all by Ruby Truly, cuid2481 (Box 180)
  - Video 1249: ES (12:00), Pinoys in Berlin (4:00 min) Both by Raymond Red, cuid2482 (Box 180)
  - Video 1250: Good McMorning America by Florence Yoo, cuid2483 (Box 180)
  - Video 1251: Hit Your Own Back by Taka Izmura, cuid2484 (Box 180)
  - Video 1252: Kinesthesia by Indu Krishnan (3:25 min), Can Dance by Ye Sook Rhee (4:00), Lament by Eiko and Koma (8:10), My Prison by HiroyaSakurai (3:30), cuid2485 (Box 180)
  - Video 1253: On Edge, Read Only (Phosphor) Memory, After Image: TTLS, In Plus/Pulse all by Norie Sato, cuid2486 (Box 180)
  - Video 1254: Tigerfly Inc./ Arnie Wong '87, cuid2487 (Box 180)
  - Video 1255: Francesca Soans, cuid2488 (Box 180)
  - Video 1256: Unidentified, cuid2489 (Box 181)
  - Video 1257: Death of an Immigrant, cuid2490 (Box 181)
  - Video 1258: Edward Akira Radtke films, cuid2491 (Box 181)
  - Video 1260: No Starch Please (2 scenes) by Ann Yen, cuid2492 (Box 181)
  - Video 1261: Rory O'Shea selected scenes, cuid2493 (Box 181)
  - Video 1262: Zu: Warrior from the Magic Mountain, cuid2494 (Box 181)
  - Video 1263: UC6, Unidentified (small " tape), cuid2495 (Box 181)
  - Video 1264: Unidentified, Chinese (small " tape), cuid2496 (Box 181)
  - Video 1265: Unidentified (small " tape), cuid2497 (Box 181)
  - Video 1266: New Cinema From India, Part 2, December 9, 1981; cuid34849 (Box 227)
  - Video 1267: Woo Art Int'l Curtain Master 1, June 23, 1988; cuid34850 (Box 227)
  - Video 1268: 1989 AAIFF Trailer (Master), July 25, 1989; cuid34851 (Box 227)
  - Video 1269: Untitled short film, Undated; cuid34852 (Box 227)
  - Video 1270: Logo Master, Undated; cuid34853 (Box 227)
  - Video 1271: CCTV Nightly Program Master, Undated; cuid34854 (Box 227)
  - Video 1272: CCTV Commercial Master, Undated; cuid34855 (Box 227)
  - Video 1273: Puppet Parade, Undated; cuid34856 (Box 227)
  - Video 1274: 1980-1982 Program Excerpts, Asian Cine-Vision / Chinese Cable TV, October, 1982; cuid34857; Contains excerpts from "Henry Street Strike," "Profile: Chinese Dance Company of NY," "Profile: Russel Baba," "Gold Mountain Dream," "The Old Soldier," and "Puppet Parade." (Box 227)
  - Video 1275: CCTV, February 2, 1983; cuid34858 (Box 227)
  - Video 1276: American Social History Project, 1877: The Grand Army of Starvation, Undated; cuid34859 (Box 227)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2498 (Box 182)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2499 (Box 183)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2500 (Box 184)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2501 (Box 185)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2502 (Box 186)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2503 (Box 187)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2504 (Box 188)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2505 (Box 189)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2506 (Box 190)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2507 (Box 191)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2508 (Box 192)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2509 (Box 193)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2510 (Box 194)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2511 (Box 195)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2512 (Box 196)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2513 (Box 197)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2514 (Box 198)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2515 (Box 199)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2516 (Box 200)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2517 (Box 201)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2518 (Box 202)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2519 (Box 203)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2520 (Box 204)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2521 (Box 205)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2522 (Box 206)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2523 (Box 207)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2524 (Box 208)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2525 (Box 209)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2526 (Box 210)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2527 (Box 211)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2528 (Box 212)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2529 (Box 213)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2530 (Box 214)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2531 (Box 215)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2532 (Box 216)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2533 (Box 217)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2534 (Box 218)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2535 (Box 219)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (Beta), cuid2536 (Box 220)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (Beta, U-Matic), cuid2537 (Box 221)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (Beta, U-Matic), cuid2538 (Box 222)
  - 2004-2007 films: Eve and the Fire Horse (2005), Who's Camus Anyway? (2006), Rain Dogs, Seven Women - Jade #2 (3 copies), Incense (3 copies), Taking Father Home (2005), cuid2539 (Box 223)
  - Harsh Canvas: The life of Henry Sugimoto, One on One with Maggie Cheung, cuid2540 (Box 224)
  - 25th AAIFF films: 6 Betacam (large), 15 Betacam (small), 5 VHS, cuid2541 (Box 225)
  - 12 large Betacam SP videos, cuid2542 (Box 226)
  - 5 U-Matics, 11VHS, cuid2543 (Box 228)
  - 35 VHS, 9 miniDVs, cuid2544 (Box 229)
  - Bridge Mechanical Final Issue - Never went to press, cuid2545 (Box 230)
  - photo: Film Festival 1994-1997, other film festivals and ACV events, cuid2546 (Box 231)
  - photo: film stills, cuid2547 (Box 232)
  - photo: slides (news slides), film stills, cuid2548 (Box 233)
  - photo: Children film series photos, cuid2549 (Box 234)
  - AAIFF, bridge mag photos, film stills, cuid2550 (Box 235)
  - Film festival photos 1 '90-92, stills 198, cuid2551 (Box 236)
  - photo: AAIFF photos, cuid2552 (Box 237)
  - photo: all stills 9/6/06, cuid2553 (Box 238)
  - 16th AAIFF trailer 35mm, cuid2554 (Box 239)
  - AAIFF Trailers 1998-2000 35 mm, cuid2555 (Box 239)
  - Maya 35mm, cuid2556 (Box 239)
  - Death and Peanuts 16mm, cuid2557 (Box 239)
  - Shorts from Mowelfund: Melvin and Mekka, Child of Manila, LAHO; A Veteran's Story; The Eagle Patrol; Matricide; to Bengali Express Final Print; Overture: Linh from Vietnam, cuid2558 (Box 242)
  - Good Kisser; Nene; Isaak, cuid2559 (Box 243)
  - 16th AAIFF Trailer; Now and Then Here and There by Fei Sing Loo; The Conductor by Jessica Yu; My America reel 2of 3; The Colours of the Sun Apricoss Swedish Film Institute; ACV Trailer 2000; Woo Art Intl ACUOpen AAIFF 94, cuid2560 (Box 244)
  - Arisa by Kalyana Shira 4 of 8, cuid2561 (Reel TAM.416.cuid2561)
  - Arisa by Kalyana Shira 3 of 8, cuid2562 (Reel TAM.416.cuid2562)
  - Arisa by Kalyana Shira 2 of 8, cuid2563 (Reel TAM.416.cuid2563)
  - Arisa by Kalyana Shira 1 of 8, cuid2564 (Reel TAM.416.cuid2564)
  - Arisa by Kalyana Shira 5 of 8, cuid2565 (Reel TAM.416.cuid2565)
  - Arisa by Kalyana Shira 6 of 8, cuid2566 (Reel TAM.416.cuid2566)
  - Arisa by Kalyana Shira 7 of 8, cuid2567 (Reel TAM.416.cuid2567)
  - Arisa by Kalyana Shira 8 of 8, cuid2568 (Reel TAM.416.cuid2568)
  - Raha by Jervekopi, cuid2569 (Reel TAM.416.cuid2569)
  - "16" 1 of 5, cuid2570 (Reel TAM.416.cuid2570)
  - "16" 2 of 5, cuid2571 (Reel TAM.416.cuid2571)
  - "16" 3 of 5, cuid2572 (Reel TAM.416.cuid2572)
  - "16" 4 of 5, cuid2573 (Reel TAM.416.cuid2573)
  - "16" 5 of 5, cuid2574 (Reel TAM.416.cuid2574)
  - The Song of Chaophaya 1 of 5, cuid2575 (Reel TAM.416.ref1035)
  - The Song of Chaophaya 2 of 5, cuid2576 (Reel TAM.416.ref1036)
  - The Song of Chaophaya 3 of 5, cuid2577 (Reel TAM.416.cuid2577)
  - The Song of Chaophaya 4 of 5, cuid2578 (Reel TAM.416.cuid2578)
  - The Song of Chaophaya 5 of 5, cuid2579 (Reel TAM.416.ref1039)
  - Memory of the Soil, cuid2580 (Reel TAM.416.cuid2580)
  - The River Chao Phraya 1 of 5, cuid2581 (Reel TAM.416.cuid2581)
  - The River Chao Phraya 2 of 5, cuid2582 (Reel TAM.416.cuid2582)
  - The River Chao Phraya 3 of 5, cuid2583 (Reel TAM.416.cuid2583)
  - The River Chao Phraya 4 of 5, cuid2584 (Reel TAM.416.cuid2584)
  - The River Chao Phraya 5 of 5, cuid2585 (Reel TAM.416.cuid2585)
  - Laser Man Peter Wang Films, cuid2586 (Reel TAM-416_ref1047_000001, Reel TAM-416_ref1047_000002, Reel TAM-416_ref1047_00003, Reel TAM-416_ref1046_000001, Reel TAM-416_ref1046_000002)
  - May Jane, cuid2588 (Reel TAM-416_ref1048_000001, Reel TAM-416_ref1048_000002, Reel TAM-416_ref1049_000001, Reel TAM-416_ref1049_000002, Reel TAM-416_ref1049_000003)
  - Southern Winds, Undated; cuid34932 (Reel cuid34932a, Reel cuid34923b, Reel cuid34932c, Reel cuid34932d, Reel cuid34932e, Reel cuid34932f)
  - Too Happy for Words, undated (Box 295, Reel 1, 2)
  - The Color of the Sun, undated (Box 295)
  - Wedding Sarees, undated (Box 295)
  - The Real Life of Pacita M., undated (Reel 302, Reel 303, Reel 301, Reel 296, Reel 297)
  - FESTIVAL, undated (Reel 304, Reel 305, Reel 307, Reel 306, Reel 308, Reel 309)
- Series V: Archived Websites, March 2014-ongoing; cuid2707; 8 websites in 8 archived websites.
  Scope and Content Note
  Asian CineVision (ACV) is a non-profit media arts organization that develops, promotes and preserves media made by or about peoples of Asian descent. Asian CineVision was founded by grassroots media activists in New York's Chinatown in 1976 to raise social and cultural awareness of the Asian American experience, both in the Asian American community and among the general public. CineVue Online is ACV's media arts journal established in 1986. The websites contains their media arts journal, information on their Asian American International Film Festival, specifically the 2014-2018 editions of the festival, news listings, event listings, trailers and descriptions of films in the festival, and press releases.
  Accruals
  http://www.asiancinevision.org/ is accrued semiannually. https://www.aaiff.org/ is accrued quarterly.
  Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.
  Appraisal
  Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of aaiff.org and asiancinevision.org in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints.